A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art AAA.finccoll
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; 14.8 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25
  - Oversized Galleys from "Jacques Kaplan's Private Collection" Exhibition Catalog, from box 15, folder 43, circa 1969 (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized Materials from "N-Dimensional Space" Exhibition, from box 16, folders 29 and 31, 1970 (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized Materials from "Projected Art: Artists at Work" Exhibition, from box 18, folder 8, 1968-1971 (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized Materials from "Two Aspects of an Illusion" Exhibition, from box 21, folder 4, 1971 (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized Poster from "Women in the Arts Festival," from box 21, folder 10, 1972 (Box OV 25)